{
  "question": "What should I do on OSRS?",
  "options": [
    {
      "optionName": "Produce",
      "answer": "Produce a certain amount of some item!",
      "question": "What kind of item?",
      "options": [
        {
          "optionName": "Bars",
          "answer": "Smelt bars!",
          "question": "What kind of bars?",
          "options": [
            {
              "optionName": "BronzeBars",
              "answer": "Bronze bars!",
              "question": "How many bronze bars?",
              "range": {
                "min": 1000,
                "max": 10000
              }
            },
            {
              "optionName": "RuneBars",
              "answer": "Runite bars!",
              "question": "How many runite bars?",
              "range": {
                "min": 50,
                "max": 500
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "optionName": "Arrows",
          "answer": "Fletch arrows!",
          "question": "What kind of arrows?",
          "options": [
            {
              "optionName": "BronzeArrows",
              "answer": "Bronze arrows!",
              "question": "How many bronze arrows?",
              "range": {
                "min": 10000,
                "max": 30000
              }
            },
            {
              "optionName": "RuneArrows",
              "answer": "Rune arrows!",
              "question": "How many rune arrows?",
              "range": {
                "min": 2000,
                "max": 10000
              }
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "optionName": "Gather",
      "answer": "Gather a certain amount of some item!",
      "question": "What kind of item?",
      "options": [
        {
          "optionName": "Logs",
          "answer": "Chop logs!",
          "question": "What kind of logs?",
          "options": [
            {
              "optionName": "NormalLogs",
              "answer": "Normal logs!",
              "question": "How many normal logs?",
              "range": {
                "min": 500,
                "max": 5000
              }
            },
            {
              "optionName": "MagicLogs",
              "answer": "Magic Logs!",
              "question": "How many magic logs?",
              "range": {
                "min": 200,
                "max": 2000
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "optionName": "Ore",
          "answer": "Mine ore!",
          "question": "What kind of ore?",
          "options": [
            {
              "optionName": "TinOre",
              "answer": "Tin ore!",
              "question": "How much tin ore?",
              "range": {
                "min": 500,
                "max": 5000
              }
            },
            {
              "optionName": "RuneOre",
              "answer": "Runite ore!",
              "question": "How much runite ore?",
              "range": {
                "min": 50,
                "max": 300
              }
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}